evrsoft.com 2005-12-10

# Privacy Policy - Evrsoft

**Your Privacy**  
| 

We respect your right to privacy and we understand that visitors to our website (evrsoft.com) need to be in control of their personal information.   
  
---|---  
  
We respect your right to privacy and we understand that visitors to our website (evrsoft.com) need to be in control of their personal information. We also want to present information on evrsoft.com that is tailored to the needs of our visitors. For this reason, we may ask you to register or to provide personal information when you visit certain areas of our site, download software, subscribe to a newsletter or join chat/forums. We will use this information to ensure the content, services, and advertising that we provide are tailored to your current and future needs. If you provide Evrsoft with your mailing address or telephone number, Evrsoft and its partners may use this information to alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information, and new services. If you provide your e-mail address, Evrsoft may contact you via e-mail as well. If you do not want Evrsoft, our alliance partners, or selected third parties to contact you, you may opt out when you provide personal information or contact Evrsoft directly. For instructions, please click on "Contact" above. If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you will still be granted to most of Evrsoft's Web sites. However, you will not have access to areas that require personal identification.

Cookies are small text files placed on your hard drive by a server. They contain only information that users volunteer, and they cannot infiltrate a user's hard drive and sneak away with personal information. The simple function of a cookie is to help the user save time and allow personalization of webpages.

> **How a Cookie Helps Evrsoft**
> 
> Cookies allows us to be more efficient. We can learn what information is important to our visitors, and what isn't. We can remove content that are not important to you and focus our efforts on things that matter to you.

You can always disable cookies by "turning off cookies" within your browser. Please consult your browser manuals for more details.

Any information you provide to Evrsoft over this website is maintained and accessible only by Evrsoft and its alliance partners. Evrsoft obtains this information to broadcast important information such as product updates and special offers. Evrsoft will not disclose any information about any individual user to entities outside of those partners except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process.

The evrsoft.com and worldwide mirror sites contains links to third-party web sites. The linked sites are not under the control of Evrsoft, and Evrsoft is not responsible for the contents of any linked site or any link contained in a linked site. Evrsoft is providing these links only as a convenience, and the inclusion of a link does not imply endorsement of the linked site by Evrsoft.

The individually identifiable information that you provide will be used extensively within the Evrsoft website to provide a personalized experience for you. Evrsoft's use of the information submitted by you may be altered to better suit visitors.

__
